





Sr. Manager seeking roles in Product/Project Management, Product Implementation, Service Delivery Management, Analytics, Stakeholder Engagement, Machine Learning, Artificial Intelligence, Tableau, Spotfire, MS Project

Total Experience: 17 Year(s) 0 Month(s)

Highest Degree: B.Com [Commerce]

Notice Period: Currently Serving Notice Period

Current Location: Bengaluru / Bangalore

Pref. Location: Bengaluru / Bangalore, United Kingdom

(UK), United States (US)

Functional Area: IT Software - Application Programming /

Maintenance

Role: Project Mar-IT/Software

Industry: IT-Software/Software Services

Verified : L Phone Number | Email - id

Marital Status: Married

Key Skills: Sr. Manager (Product Implementation Lead), Program Manager, IT Project Management, Product Management, Analytics, Service Delivery Management, Stakeholder Engagement, Process Improvement, Machine

Learning, Artificial Intelligence, Tableau, Spotfire, Python

Last Active: 21-Jan-21 Last Modified: 21-Jan-21

Jump to Section

Work Experience | Education | IT Skills |

Summary

Professional with 17 years of experience in managing the entire gamut of Product Implementation; delivering of analytics and reporting solutions, and driving projects to successful completion

Successfully grew revenue of \$1.2 Million by expanding footprint of Genpact SharePoint services within the client organization

Played a key role as Lead Product Implementation and Service Delivery Manager for US & India IT teams and have strategically executed many innovation projects

Expertise in setting out delivery standards for various operational areas, implementing quality procedures to facilitate a high-quality experience, while adhering to the SLA and business services

Maintained cordial relationship with all the clients by understanding their requirement & delivering custom solution.

Work Experience

- Genpact as Implementation Lead Aug 2011 to May 2020
- Genpact as Sr. Manager (Engagement Lead Analytics) Aug 2011 to Apr 2020

Key Result Areas:

Managed Reports and Deployment work-streams; managed implementation of PVAI (Pharmacovigilance Al product) Identified reporting requirements and translated them into specifications for development team

Ensured reports are developed to specifications within agreed timeline and tested prior to client UAT by collaborating with product management and engineering teams

Conducted workshop with business teams to define key business considerations that need to be addressed prior to and during deployment

Demonstrated ability to generate innovative solutions to problems and effectively work with and communicate with key partners

Oversaw departmental training activities to ensure all team members received functional product expertise

Tailored each project, discovering process improvements & improving client efficiencies

Defined the deployment strategy and implementation plan of the product

Highlights

Sr. Manager (Onsite Engagement Lead), New York

Headed onsite client relations for top 5 pharmaceutical companies in New York through leading a team of 5 onsite leads

Took proactive proposals to clients through exploring potential clients/buying centers for Genpact Conducted:

o Quarterly Business Review meetings with client PMO to review program performance, gaps, risks and mitigation plan

o Periodic review sessions with onsite leads to review the health of their respective service lines

Acted as an escalation point and ensured their bridging, including initiation of any necessary escalations and business impacting issues

Successfully maintained high NPS score



Important

 Using Free CV Search you have access to featured candidate profiles of Naukri. You can browse through the profiles and email the candidates of your choice directly using the email option provided. To prevent misuse of candidate information, contact details and attached resume of the candidates have been withheld. Manager (Service Delivery Manager), Bengaluru

Led a team of 85 professionals for the overall delivery of Analytics services including account planning, revenue and resource forecasting

Assist onsite sales team in identifying new buying centers and opportunities

Participate in RFI/RFP/proactive proposal development process which includes representing capabilities, experience, solution and pricing

Conducted recruitment of new employees; led employee training and development by monitoring competency grids and identified training needs for skill / competency up-gradation

Assistant Manager (Project Manager), Bengaluru

Delivered analytics projects for different business functions including sales, marketing, commercial operations, training, medical & so on

Headed end-to-end project from requirement gathering, estimation, project charter, build to UAT; created project documentation such as issue tracking, functional gaps, risks and changes

Genpact as Onsite Engagement Lead - Analytics Aug 2011 to Apr 2020

Ernst & Young as Sr. Customer Support Analyst Jan 2007 to Dec 2010

Highlights:

Acted as SPOC for Asia Pacific region for Remedy tool; owned entire implementation process for Remedy within the area and oversee implementations are conducted in an efficient and organized manner

Delivered training for new users, new deployments, upgrades & conducted refresher training while attending Global Deployments meetings

Understood key requirements of firm and regulators risk management rules and policies; used analytical and project management methodology and tools

Completed all assigned projects/tasks in line with the standard operating procedures; ensured completeness, accuracy and appropriateness of all task assigned

Facilitated and drove the process to completion by timely following up on requests from Onshore

Conducted meetings with the account teams including Partner, Senior Manager, and Business Development to identify potential clients that needs to be linked and liaison with the respective partner for approvals

America Online as Sr. Quality Assurance Analyst Oct 2002 to Dec 2006

Highlights:

Conducted calibration session with the leadership for Abuquerque, Delhi and Oklahoma for site performance evaluation

Reported to the Quality Assurance Manager while monitoring calls for 10 global sites for SLA compliance Analyzed & prepared QAA Analysis report to understand QAA performance of the entire Quality team

^ Back to Top

Education

UG: B.Com (Commerce) from St. Josephs College of Commerce in 2001

Other Qualifications/Certifications/Programs:

Advanced Analytics

^ Back to Top

IT Skills

Skill Name	Version Last Used	Experience
MS Project		
Python		
SQL		
TABLEAU		
SPOTFIRE		
Advanced excel/VBA		

^ Back to Top

Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak
English				
Hindi				
Kannada				
Tamil				

^ Back to Top

Affirmative Action

Work Authorization

^ Back to Top

Careers - About Us - Clients - Terms & Conditions - FAQs - Contact Us - Report a Problem - Site Map - Resources
Our Partners: Jeevansathi Matrimonials - ICIClcommunities.org - 99acres - Real Estate In India
All rights reserved © 2021 Info Edge India Ltd.

Careers - About Us - Clients - Terms & Conditions - FAQ's - Contact Us - Report a Problem - Site Map - Resources Our Partners: Jeevansathi Matrimonials - ICIClcommunities.org - 99acres - Real Estate In India All rights reserved © 2021 Info Edge India Ltd.